MÁRCIO JOSÉ GURKA JÚNIOR

115 São Jerônimo da Serra Street, Ponta Grossa, Paraná, CEP 84053220 | 55(42)9982-4591 | marciogurkajr@gmail.com | LinkedIn: https://br.linkedin.com/in/marciogurkajr

Summary

Born in 1995, nowadays working as an intern at the Information Technology Hub of Ponta Grossa State University, and as an innovation projects researcher and developer at DF Systems, a startup located at Ponta Grossa, Paraná, Brazil. Also in the last year of his bachelor's degree Computer Engineering. Also voluntarily participates of some projects, like EJEC (Junior Company of Computer Engineering) as a project advisor and programmer, and a scientific research to improve and facilitates the access of information to people.

Programming Skills

Strong skills in: C, PHP, Java, JavaScript, GIT, AngularJS, jQuery, CSS, HTML, Twitter Boostrap, MySQL,

PostgreSQL, Sybase, Laravel, NodeJS

Familiar with: Ruby on Rails, Python, MongoDB, C#, WebRTC

General Skills

Strong skills in: object oriented design/programming, web development, Database modeling and maintenance, Software Development, Teamwork, Entrepreneurship, Research, Innovation, Reverse Engineering, Image Manipulation (Adobe Photoshop), Creative, Proative, Good Worker, Management.

Professional Experience

Systems Analysis intern, 6/2014 to Present – Information Technology Hub of Ponta Grossa State University, Ponta Grossa, Paraná

Improved Backend and Frontend developer of Institutional Research Management System; Maintenance of academic systems; Technical support for users; Improved and maintaned institutional databases systems.

Innovation Researcher and Developer, 6/2015 to Present – DF Systems, Ponta Grossa, Paraná Innovation projects in Javascript, NodeJS; Creation of new products.

Volunteer programmer and project advisor, 7/2015 to Present – EJEC (Junior Company of Computer Engineering), Ponta Grossa, Paraná

Consultancy and development of technological solutions.

Volunteer, 1/2013 to 12/2015 – Computer Museum UEPG, Ponta Grossa, Paraná

Creation of products using recyclable materials of computers, production of educational robotic workshops.

Education

SANT'ANA HIGH SCHOOL AND UNIVERSITY – Ponta Grossa, Paraná Computer Science Technician, 12/2011
Improved Programming Skills; Hardware Maintenance

PONTA GROSSA STATE UNIVERSITY – Ponta Grossa, Paraná **Bachelor's degree Computer Engineering,** Expected to 12/2016

Emphasis in Software Development, Programming Languages and Hardware Building

PARANÁ FEDERAL TECHNOLOGY UNIVERSITY – Ponta Grossa, Paraná English (Intermediate), 12/2013

Improved English Language. Workload: 320 hours

INFLUX ENGLISH SCHOOL – Ponta Grossa, Paraná **English (Advanced)**, Expected to 06/2017 Improved English Language

PONTA GROSSA STATE UNIVERSITY – Ponta Grossa, Paraná **Software Build Management**, 8/2014 Improved knowledgment of GIT skills. Workload: 20 hours

PONTA GROSSA STATE UNIVERSITY – Ponta Grossa, Paraná Laravel – AngularJS Software Development, 11/2015 Improved AngularJS and Laravel skills. Workload: 20 hours

* Several other courses involving programming languages, software management, people management, project management and innovation.

Other Interests

Entrepreneurship, learning languages, agile software development, music, technology, innovation, books, computing, games, photography, sports, learning programming languages, running, traveling